[{"question":"1. Which action is performed by a client when establishing communication with a server via the use of UDP at the transport layer?","answers":[{"text":"The client sets the window size for the session.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The client sends an ISN to the server to start the 3-way handshake.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The client randomly selects a source port number.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The client sends a synchronization segment to begin the session.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"2. Which transport layer feature is used to guarantee session establishment?","answers":[{"text":"UDP ACK flag","isCorrect":false},{"text":"TCP 3-way handshake","isCorrect":true},{"text":"UDP sequence number","isCorrect":false},{"text":"TCP port number","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"3. What is the complete range of TCP and UDP well-known ports?","answers":[{"text":"0 to 255","isCorrect":false},{"text":"0 to 1023","isCorrect":true},{"text":"256 – 1023","isCorrect":false},{"text":"1024 – 49151","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"4. What is a socket?","answers":[{"text":"the combination of the source and destination IP address and source and destination Ethernet address","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the combination of a source IP address and port number or a destination IP address and port number","isCorrect":true},{"text":"the combination of the source and destination sequence and acknowledgment numbers","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the combination of the source and destination sequence numbers and port numbers","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"5. A PC is downloading a large file from a server. The TCP window is 1000 bytes. The server is sending the file using 100-byte segments. How many segments will the server send before it requires an acknowledgment from the PC?","answers":[{"text":"1 segment","isCorrect":false},{"text":"10 segments","isCorrect":true},{"text":"100 segments","isCorrect":false},{"text":"1000 segments","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"7. What does a client do when it has UDP datagrams to send?","answers":[{"text":"It just sends the datagrams.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"It queries the server to see if it is ready to receive data.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It sends a simplified three-way handshake to the server.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It sends to the server a segment with the SYN flag set to synchronize the conversation.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"8. Which three fields are used in a UDP segment header? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"Window Size","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Length","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Source Port","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Acknowledgment Number","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Checksum","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Sequence Number","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"9. What are two roles of the transport layer in data communication on a network? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"identifying the proper application for each communication stream","isCorrect":true},{"text":"tracking the individual communication between applications on the source and destination hosts","isCorrect":true},{"text":"providing frame delimiting to identify bits making up a frame","isCorrect":false},{"text":"performing a cyclic redundancy check on the frame for errors","isCorrect":false},{"text":"providing the interface between applications and the underlying network over which messages are transmitted","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Explanation:","answers":[{"text":"Tracking the individual communication streams between applications on the source and destination hosts","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Segmenting data at the source and reassembling the data at the destination","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Identifying the proper application for each communication stream through the use of port numbers","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"10. What information is used by TCP to reassemble and reorder received segments?","answers":[{"text":"port numbers","isCorrect":false},{"text":"sequence numbers","isCorrect":true},{"text":"acknowledgment numbers","isCorrect":false},{"text":"fragment numbers","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"12. Which two characteristics are associated with UDP sessions? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"Destination devices receive traffic with minimal delay.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Transmitted data segments are tracked.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Destination devices reassemble messages and pass them to an application.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Received data is unacknowledged.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Unacknowledged data packets are retransmitted.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"16. What is a characteristic of UDP?","answers":[{"text":"UDP datagrams take the same path and arrive in the correct order at the destination.​","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Applications that use UDP are always considered unreliable.​","isCorrect":false},{"text":"UDP reassembles the received datagrams in the order they were received.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"UDP only passes data to the network when the destination is ready to receive the data.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"17. What kind of port must be requested from IANA in order to be used with a specific application?","answers":[{"text":"registered port","isCorrect":true},{"text":"private port","isCorrect":false},{"text":"dynamic port","isCorrect":false},{"text":"source port","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"18. Which three application layer protocols use TCP? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"SMTP","isCorrect":true},{"text":"FTP","isCorrect":true},{"text":"SNMP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"HTTP","isCorrect":true},{"text":"TFTP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"DHCP","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"19. Which three statements characterize UDP? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"UDP provides basic connectionless transport layer functions.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"UDP provides connection-oriented, fast transport of data at Layer 3.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"UDP relies on application layer protocols for error detection.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"UDP is a low overhead protocol that does not provide sequencing or flow control mechanisms.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"UDP relies on IP for error detection and recovery.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"UDP provides sophisticated flow control mechanisms.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"21. Which field in the TCP header indicates the status of the three-way handshake process?","answers":[{"text":"window","isCorrect":false},{"text":"reserved","isCorrect":false},{"text":"checksum","isCorrect":false},{"text":"control bits","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"22. Why does HTTP use TCP as the transport layer protocol?","answers":[{"text":"to ensure the fastest possible download speed","isCorrect":false},{"text":"because HTTP is a best-effort protocol","isCorrect":false},{"text":"because transmission errors can be tolerated easily","isCorrect":false},{"text":"because HTTP requires reliable delivery","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"24. How are port numbers used in the TCP/IP encapsulation process?","answers":[{"text":"Source port numbers and destination port numbers are not necessary when UDP is the transport layer protocol being used for the communication.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Source port and destination port numbers are randomly generated.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"If multiple conversations occur that are using the same service, the source port number is used to track the separate conversations.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Destination port numbers are assigned automatically and cannot be changed.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"25. In what two situations would UDP be better than TCP as the preferred transport protocol? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"when applications need to guarantee that a packet arrives intact, in sequence, and unduplicated","isCorrect":false},{"text":"when a faster delivery mechanism is needed","isCorrect":true},{"text":"when delivery overhead is not an issue","isCorrect":false},{"text":"when applications do not need to guarantee delivery of the data","isCorrect":true},{"text":"when destination port numbers are dynamic","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"26. What are three responsibilities of the transport layer? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"meeting the reliability requirements of applications, if any","isCorrect":true},{"text":"multiplexing multiple communication streams from many users or applications on the same network","isCorrect":true},{"text":"identifying the applications and services on the client and server that should handle transmitted data","isCorrect":true},{"text":"directing packets towards the destination network","isCorrect":false},{"text":"formatting data into a compatible form for receipt by the destination devices","isCorrect":false},{"text":"conducting error detection of the contents in frames","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"28. Which two protocols may devices use in the application process that sends email? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"HTTP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"SMTP","isCorrect":true},{"text":"POP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"IMAP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"DNS","isCorrect":true},{"text":"POP3","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"29. What is true about the Server Message Block protocol?","answers":[{"text":"Different SMB message types have a different format.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Clients establish a long term connection to servers.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"SMB messages cannot authenticate a session.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"SMB uses the FTP protocol for communication.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"30. What is the function of the HTTP GET message?","answers":[{"text":"to request an HTML page from a web server","isCorrect":true},{"text":"to send error information from a web server to a web client","isCorrect":false},{"text":"to upload content to a web server from a web client","isCorrect":false},{"text":"to retrieve client email from an email server using TCP port 110","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"31. Which OSI layer provides the interface between the applications used to communicate and the underlying network over which messages are transmitted?","answers":[{"text":"application","isCorrect":true},{"text":"presentation","isCorrect":false},{"text":"session","isCorrect":false},{"text":"transport","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"32. Which networking model is being used when an author uploads one chapter document to a file server of a book publisher?","answers":[{"text":"peer-to-peer","isCorrect":false},{"text":"master-slave","isCorrect":false},{"text":"client/server","isCorrect":true},{"text":"point-to-point","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"33. What do the client/server and peer-to-peer network models have in common?","answers":[{"text":"Both models have dedicated servers.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Both models support devices in server and client roles.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Both models require the use of TCP/IP-based protocols.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Both models are used only in the wired network environment.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"34. In what networking model would eDonkey, eMule, BitTorrent, Bitcoin, and LionShare be used?","answers":[{"text":"peer-to-peer","isCorrect":true},{"text":"client-based","isCorrect":false},{"text":"master-slave","isCorrect":false},{"text":"point-to-point","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"35. What is a common protocol that is used with peer-to-peer applications such as WireShare, Bearshare, and Shareaza?","answers":[{"text":"Ethernet","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Gnutella","isCorrect":true},{"text":"POP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"SMTP","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"37. The application layer of the TCP/IP model performs the functions of what three layers of the OSI model? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"physical","isCorrect":false},{"text":"session","isCorrect":true},{"text":"network","isCorrect":false},{"text":"presentation","isCorrect":true},{"text":"data link","isCorrect":false},{"text":"transport","isCorrect":false},{"text":"application","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"38. What is an example of network communication that uses the client-server model?","answers":[{"text":"A user uses eMule to download a file that is shared by a friend after the file location is determined.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A workstation initiates an ARP to find the MAC address of a receiving host.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A user prints a document by using a printer that is attached to a workstation of a coworker.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A workstation initiates a DNS request when the user types www.cisco.com in the address bar of a web browser.","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"39. Which layer in the TCP/IP model is used for formatting, compressing, and encrypting data?","answers":[{"text":"internetwork","isCorrect":false},{"text":"session","isCorrect":false},{"text":"presentation","isCorrect":false},{"text":"application","isCorrect":true},{"text":"network access","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"40. What is an advantage of SMB over FTP?​","answers":[{"text":"Only with SMB can data transfers occur in both directions.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Only SMB establishes two simultaneous connections with the client, making the data transfer faster.​","isCorrect":false},{"text":"SMB is more reliable than FTP because SMB uses TCP and FTP uses UDP.​","isCorrect":false},{"text":"SMB clients can establish a long-term connection to the server.​","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"41. A manufacturing company subscribes to certain hosted services from its ISP. The services that are required include hosted world wide web, file transfer, and e-mail. Which protocols represent these three key applications? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"FTP","isCorrect":true},{"text":"HTTP","isCorrect":true},{"text":"DNS","isCorrect":false},{"text":"SNMP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"DHCP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"SMTP","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"43. What type of information is contained in a DNS MX record?","answers":[{"text":"the FQDN of the alias used to identify a service","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the IP address for an FQDN entry","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the domain name mapped to mail exchange servers","isCorrect":true},{"text":"the IP address of an authoritative name server","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"44. Which three protocols operate at the application layer of the TCP/IP model? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"ARP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"TCP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"UDP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"FTP","isCorrect":true},{"text":"POP3","isCorrect":true},{"text":"DHCP","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"45. Which protocol is used by a client to communicate securely with a web server?","answers":[{"text":"SMTP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"SMB","isCorrect":false},{"text":"IMAP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"HTTPS","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"46. Which applications or services allow hosts to act as client and server at the same time?","answers":[{"text":"client/server applications","isCorrect":false},{"text":"email applications","isCorrect":false},{"text":"P2P applications","isCorrect":true},{"text":"authentication services","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"48. Which scenario describes a function provided by the transport layer?","answers":[{"text":"A student is using a classroom VoIP phone to call home. The unique identifier burned into the phone is a transport layer address used to contact another network device on the same network.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A student is playing a short web-based movie with sound. The movie and sound are encoded within the transport layer header.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A student has two web browser windows open in order to access two web sites. The transport layer ensures the correct web page is delivered to the correct browser window.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"A corporate worker is accessing a web server located on a corporate network. The transport layer formats the screen so the web page appears properly no matter what device is being used to view the web site.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"49. Which three layers of the OSI model provide similar network services to those provided by the application layer of the TCP/IP model? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"physical layer","isCorrect":false},{"text":"session layer","isCorrect":true},{"text":"transport layer","isCorrect":false},{"text":"application layer","isCorrect":true},{"text":"presentation layer","isCorrect":true},{"text":"data link layer","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"50. A PC that is communicating with a web server has a TCP window size of 6,000 bytes when sending data and a packet size of 1,500 bytes. Which byte of information will the web server acknowledge after it has received two packets of data from the PC?","answers":[{"text":"3001","isCorrect":true},{"text":"6001","isCorrect":false},{"text":"4500","isCorrect":false},{"text":"6000","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"51. A PC that is communicating with a web server has a TCP window size of 6,000 bytes when sending data and a packet size of 1,500 bytes. Which byte of information will the web server acknowledge after it has received three packets of data from the PC?","answers":[{"text":"4501","isCorrect":true},{"text":"6001","isCorrect":false},{"text":"6000","isCorrect":false},{"text":"4500","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"52. A PC that is communicating with a web server has a TCP window size of 6,000 bytes when sending data and a packet size of 1,500 bytes. Which byte of information will the web server acknowledge after it has received four packets of data from the PC?","answers":[{"text":"6001","isCorrect":true},{"text":"3001","isCorrect":false},{"text":"1501","isCorrect":false},{"text":"1500","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"53. A client creates a packet to send to a server. The client is requesting TFTP service. What number will be used as the destination port number in the sending packet?","answers":[{"text":"69","isCorrect":true},{"text":"67","isCorrect":false},{"text":"53","isCorrect":false},{"text":"80","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"54. A client creates a packet to send to a server. The client is requesting FTP service. What number will be used as the destination port number in the sending packet?","answers":[{"text":"21","isCorrect":true},{"text":"69","isCorrect":false},{"text":"67","isCorrect":false},{"text":"80","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"55. A client creates a packet to send to a server. The client is requesting SSH service. What number will be used as the destination port number in the sending packet?","answers":[{"text":"22","isCorrect":true},{"text":"69","isCorrect":false},{"text":"67","isCorrect":false},{"text":"80","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"56. A client creates a packet to send to a server. The client is requesting HTTP service. What number will be used as the destination port number in the sending packet?","answers":[{"text":"80","isCorrect":true},{"text":"67","isCorrect":false},{"text":"53","isCorrect":false},{"text":"69","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"57. A client creates a packet to send to a server. The client is requesting POP3 service. What number will be used as the destination port number in the sending packet?","answers":[{"text":"110","isCorrect":true},{"text":"67","isCorrect":false},{"text":"53","isCorrect":false},{"text":"69","isCorrect":false},{"text":"443","isCorrect":false},{"text":"161","isCorrect":false},{"text":"80","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"58. A client creates a packet to send to a server. The client is requesting telnet service. What number will be used as the destination port number in the sending packet?","answers":[{"text":"23","isCorrect":true},{"text":"443","isCorrect":false},{"text":"161","isCorrect":false},{"text":"110","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"59. A client creates a packet to send to a server. The client is requesting SNMP service. What number will be used as the destination port number in the sending packet?","answers":[{"text":"161","isCorrect":true},{"text":"443","isCorrect":false},{"text":"110","isCorrect":false},{"text":"80","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"60. A client creates a packet to send to a server. The client is requesting SMTP service. What number will be used as the destination port number in the sending packet?","answers":[{"text":"25","isCorrect":true},{"text":"443","isCorrect":false},{"text":"161","isCorrect":false},{"text":"110","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"61. A client creates a packet to send to a server. The client is requesting HTTPS service. What number will be used as the destination port number in the sending packet?","answers":[{"text":"443","isCorrect":true},{"text":"161","isCorrect":false},{"text":"110","isCorrect":false},{"text":"80","isCorrect":false}]}]